Guide to the Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
- Drawings, 1924-2004
  - Durham Coca-Cola Bottling Company, 1961 (Tube 739)
    Sections, Elevations, Site Plans
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Durham (N.C.)
  - Durham County Office Building, 1967 (Tube 827)
    Planting Plan, Site Plan
    Davis Archie Royal 1907-1980; Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Durham Drapery Company, 1963 (Tube 827)
  - Durham Golf Course (Tube 552)
    Topographic Map
  - Durham Housing Authority: Fayetteville Street, 1984 (Tube 437)
    Planting details
  - Durham Housing Authority: Forest Hill Heights, 1983-1984 (Tube 437)
    Proposed rose garden, conceptual plan
  - Durham Housing Authority: Project NC 13-11 (1 of 2), 1969 (Tube 782)
    Topographic and utility map, design development plan
    Carr, Harrison, Pruden & DePasquale; Boney and Newcomb; Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Durham Housing Authority: Project NC 13-11 (2 of 2), 1969 (Tube 751)
  - Durham Housing Authority: Project NC 13-13, 1980 (Tube 816)
    Site analysis, demolition plan, landscape plan
  - Durham Ringling Street area (Tube 552)
  - Eagle Nest (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Flatfolder 2)
    Bell Design Group; Surry County (N.C.)
  - Eagle Nest (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Flatfolder 1)
  - Eagle Nest (1 of 2), 1982 (Tube 6)
    Master Development Plan, Site Analysis, Architectural Design
  - Eagle Nest (2 of 2), 1982 (Tube 320)
  - Eagle Nest (Tube 161)
    Master development plan, topography
  - Eagle Nest Golf Course (Tube 878)
    Bell Design Group; North Myrtle Beach (S.C.)
  - Earl property, 1980 (Tube 478)
    Conceptual terrain and natural systems analysis
  - The East Carolina Bank: Roanoke Island Office, 1970 (Tube 704)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Shields-Wyatt Architects; Manteo (N.C.)
  - East Carolina University (1 of 2), 1997 (Tube 443)
    Rawl and General Classroom Building Site Improvements, Library Drive Site Improvement Plan, Landscape Plan, Scott Hall Courtyard Decorative Fencing
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Greenville (N.C.)
  - East Carolina University (2 of 2), 1997 (Tube 815)
    Scott Hall Courtyard Decorative Fencing
  - East Carolina University, 1995-1997 (Tube 438)
    Rawl and General Classroom Building, Site Improvements, Landscape Plans, Scott Hal Courtyard Decorative Fencing, Library Drive Site Improvement Plan
  - East Carolina University, 1996 (Tube 362)
    survey
    Rivers & Associates, Inc; Greenville (N.C.)
  - East Carolina University: Joyner Library addition and renovation (1 of 2), 1996 (Tube 176)
    Contract document and submittal
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Walter, Robbs, Callahan, & Pierce Architects PA; Greenville (N.C.)
  - East Carolina University: Joyner Library addition and renovation (2 of 2), 1996 (Tube 177)
    Walter, Robbs, Callahan, & Pierce Architects PA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Greenville (N.C.)
  - East Carolina University: Library Drive, 1996-1997 (Tube 452)
    Revised Irrigation, Utility Plans, Utility Conflicts, Topographic Cross-sections, Site Plans, Index of Sheets
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; North Carolina Division of Highways; Greenville (N.C.)
  - East Carolina University: Library Drive (1 of 2), 1996 (Tube 440)
    Library Drive Contract Phases II and III, Building Demolition Contract, Library Drive Site Improvements
  - East Carolina University: Library Drive (2 of 2), 1996 (Tube 115)
    Greenville (N.C.)
  - East Wake County Consolidated High School (1 of 2), 1963 (Tube 287)
  - East Wake County Consolidated High School (2 of 2), 1963 (Tube 824)
    Planting plan, grading and drainage plan
  - East Wayne County High School (Tube 704)
    Griffin Billy AIA; Wayne County (N.C.)
  - Eastowne Apartments (1 of 2), 1968-1969 (Tube 641)
    Vicinity map and site details, plan and profile of access road, sanitary sewer plan and profile, water line plans and electrical details, utility plan
  - Eastowne Apartments (2 of 2), 1968-1969 (Tube 642)
    Proposed site utilities development, water and sewer system, street intersections, lighting and garbage stations, site plan development, grading plan, west access road, site development study plan
  - Eastowne Subdivision, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Supplementary Drawings
    Cannon John M.; Richard C. Bell Associates; Orange County (N.C.)
  - Eastowne Subdivision, 1968 (Tube 822)
    Preliminary sewer design
  - Eastowne Subdivision, 1967-1968 (Tube 823)
    Master Development plan, land use breakdown
  - Eaton Corporation: Industrial Truck Division Greenville Plant (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Tube 858)
    Total Site Plan, Plans and Details, Irrigation Plan, Planting Plan
    J. H. Hudson, Inc.; Bell Design Group; Greenville (N.C.)
  - Eaton Corporation: Industrial Truck Division Greenville Plant (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Tube 858)
    Total Site Plan, Elevations
  - Eddy (Dr. and Mrs. David) residence, 1981 (Flatfolder 23)
    Photographic Negative: Land Survey
    Smith and Smith Surveyors; Chapel Hill Township (N.C.)
  - Eddy (Dr. and Mrs. David) residence, 1982 (Tube 843)
    Master Plans, Construction Details, Site Plans
    Bell Design Group; Chapel Hill Township (N.C.)
  - Edenton Bay (1 of 5), 1992 (Flatfolder 10)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Chowan County (N.C.)
  - Edenton Bay (2 of 5), 1992 (Flatfolder 11)
  - Edenton Bay (3 of 5), 1992 (Tube 228)
    Concept master plan of new town
  - Edenton Bay (4 of 5), 1992 (Tube 461)
    Concept Master Plan of a New Town, Site Plans
  - Edenton Bay (5 of 5), 1992 (Tube 539)
    Phases I and II Development
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Edenton (N.C.)
  - Edenton Bay (Tube 347)
    Master plan of new town
  - Edenton Bay, 1993 (Tube 351)
    Concept master plan
  - Edenton Bay (Tube 469)
    Community Site Plan
  - Edenton Bay, 1992-1993 (Tube 509)
    Concept Master Plans of a New Town; Site Plans, Typical Block near Town Center, Phases I and II Development
  - Edenton Bay (Tube 58)
  - Edna Wells Park, 1968 (Tube 456)
  - Edna Wells Park: Raleigh Parks and Recreation Commission (1 of 2), 1968 (Tube 51)
    Lighting plan, details
  - Edna Wells Park: Raleigh Parks and Recreation Commission (2 of 2), 1968 (Tube 52)
  - Edwards Dance Studio, 1974 (Tube 706)
    Preliminary Plans
  - Edwards Ridge Subdivision Lot 5, 2003 (Tube 231)
    Philip Post and Associates Inc.; Chatham County (N.C.)
  - Edwards (Dr. and Mrs. J.R., Jr.) residence, 1963 (Tube 712)
    Staking and Grading Plan, Constructing and Planting Details, Planting Plan
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Fuquay Springs (N.C.)
  - Eggeleston (Tony and Ellen) residence (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Tube 838)
    Grading and Drainage Plans, Site Plan, Sections and Pool Plan, Floor Plan with Electrical, Exploded Elevations, Southwest Elevation, Heat and Air Conditioning, Roofing Plan, Foundation Plan, Elevations and Schedules, Foundation Plan: Sections and Details, Staking/Dimensions, Elevations
  - Eggeleston (Tony and Ellen) residence (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Tube 839)
    General Staking, Grading and Drainage, Southwest Elevation, Floor Plans and Schedules: Heat and Air Conditioning, Electrical and Lighting, Floor Plans and Schedules, Detail Plans, Site Plan, Staking Plan, Plumbing Plan, Foundation Plan
  - Eggeleston (Tony and Ellen) residence, 1983 (Tube 868)
    Southwest Elevation, Floor Plan
  - Eggleston (Tony and Ellen) Villa Terra, 1983 (Tube 283)
    Southwest elevation, floor plans
  - Eggleston (Tony and Ellen) Villa Terra (Tube 691)
    Southwest Elevations, Floor Plans, Details, and Sections, Plumbing Plan, Door and Window Schedule, Foundation Plan, Mechanical Plan, Elevations, Roof Framing Plan
  - Ellington (William and Meta) residence, 1980-1981 (Tube 842)
    Construction Details, Planting Plans, Site Plan, Master Plans, Staking Plans
  - Elliott (Mr. and Mrs. A.G., Jr.) residence, 1964 (Tube 847)
    Site Plans, Plans and Details, Planting Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Fuquay Springs (N.C.)
  - Elliott (Mr. and Mrs. Stuart), 1973-1974 (Tube 706)
    Site Plan, Planting Plan, Details, Elevations, Pool Staking Plan, Landscape Lighting Plan
  - Elon College, 1965-1966 (Tube 603)
    Topographic Map, Detail Planting Plans, Plot Map, Entrance Wall, Married Student Housing, Preliminary Utilities Plan, Existing Utilities Plan, Plot Plan, Schedules and Details
    Guy E. Crampton and Associates; Elon (N.C.)
  - Elon College, 1940-1966 (Tube 538)
    Preliminary Plot Plan, Water and Sewer Systems Plans, Planting Plans, Topographic Map, Plat Map, Plot Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; McAdams J. Mark Surveyor; Linberg A. C. Consulting Engineer; Guy E. Crampton and Associates; Elon (N.C.)
  - Elon College, 1966 (Tube 704)
    Master Parking and Walk Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Elon (N.C.)
  - Elon College, 1967 (Tube 847)
    Master Planting Plan, Master Parking and Walk Plan, Plant List-Details, Detail Planting Plans, Site Plan
  - Elon College: Library plaza and fountain area, 1969 (Tube 762)
    Richard C. Bell Associates
  - Elon College: Library plaza and fountain area, 1968 (Tube 761)
  - Emerald Isle Realty Office, 1992 (Tube 230)
    Second floor plan, basement floor plan, building section
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Emerald Isle (N.C.)
  - Energy and Exhibition Center: Southern Living Show, 1980 (Tube 49)
  - Energy Efficient Features of Prototype Shelter (Tube 224)
    Sun-earth theme pre-cut timber homes
  - Epworth Methodist Church, 1962 (Tube 167)
    Landscape plan and details, elevations
  - The Ervin Company Information Center, 1970 (Tube 710)
    Landscape Plan, Details, Planting Plan, Grading Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Ferebee, Walters and Associates; Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Erwin Mill Farm, 1978 (Tube 164)
    Fairmont (Ga.)
  - Ethridge (Mr. and Mrs. Mark) residence, 1966 (Tube 853)
    Site Plan and Details, Entrance Gate Plan, Sections, and Details, Plan of Walk to River
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Sanford (N.C.)
  - Eure-Winston Property (1 of 2), 1970 (Tube 645)
  - Eure-Winston Property (2 of 2), 1970 (Tube 745)
    Schematic Site Development Plan
  - Eure-Winston Property (Tube 724)
    Master Development Plan
  - Evans (Mr. and Mrs. David), 1964 (Tube 704)
    Staking Plan, Landscape Plan, Elevation
  - Evans (Mr. and Mrs. E.H.) residence, 1966 (Tube 853)
    Preliminary Landscape Plan; Site Plans
    Richard C. Bell Associates; MacMillan & MacMillan Architects; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Evans (Mr. and Mrs. E.H.) residence, 1966-1967 (Tube 704)
    Revised Site Development Plan and Planting Plan, Details
  - Evans (William E.) residence, 1974 (Tube 507)
  - Exchange Plaza, 1962 (Tube 762)
  - Exchange Plaza (1 of 3), 1963 (Tube 724)
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; F. Carter Williams, Architects; Odell Associates Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Exchange Plaza (2 of 3), 1963 (Tube 751)
    Grading plan, utility plan
  - Exchange Plaza (3 of 3), 1963 (Tube 50)
    F. Carter Williams, Architects; Odell Associates Inc.; Bell Richard C. 1928-; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Exchange Plaza (Tube 167)
    Plan of plantings
  - F. T. Green and Associates: Office facilities and grounds, 1981 (Tube 843)
    Site Plan, Landscape Development Plan, Staking Plan, Planting Plan, Construction Details
  - Faircloth (Mr. and Mrs. Lauch) residence (Tube 486)
    Bell Design Group; Clinton (N.C.)
  - Fairmont City School Board of Education, 1977 (Tube 118)
    Topographic survey, high school master development plan
    Bell Design Group; Fairmont (N.C.)
  - Fairmont High School, 1976 (Tube 125)
    Site plans, addition, profiles
    Hayes-Howell & Associates; Bell Design Group; Fairmont (N.C.)
  - Fairmont High School: Athletic facilities, 1977 (Tube 772)
    Preliminary grading and storm drainage, staking, planting, erosion and sediment control, construction details, alternates
  - Fairmont Senior High School (Tube 124)
    Existing grade of football stadium site
    Fairmont (N.C.)
  - Farr Airport, 1970 (Tube 871)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Georgetown County (S.C.)
  - Farrington Farm, 1975 (Tube 775)
    Livery, residence, elevations, floor plans
  - Fayetteville and vicinity official map, 1969 (Tube 6)
    Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Beautiful: Franklin Streetscape, 1978 (Tube 771)
    Dick Street planting and visual improvement, construction details, irrigation
  - Fayetteville Garden Council: Hands Project, 1966 (Tube 264)
    Rowan Street overpass, Grove Street city maintenance area, intersection - Bordeaux shopping center, Tarts TV Bragg Boulevard, Bragg Boulevard at Crossover
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field) (1 of 2), 1968 (Tube 793)
    Grading Plan, Lighting Studies, Planting Plan Details for an Airways Terminal Building
    Hicks-Willis Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field) (2 of 2), 1968 (Tube 160)
    Preliminary site plan
    Hicks Mason S.; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field) (1 of 2), 1968-1969 (Tube 826)
    Planting Plan, Preliminary Site Plan, Site Plans, Parking Area Irrigation Plans
    Hicks Mason S.; Hicks-Willis Architects; John Talbert & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field) (2 of 2), 1968-1969 (Tube 720)
    Irrigation Plan, Planting Plan Details, Parking Area Planting Plan, Preliminary Site Plans, Parking Area Irrigation Plan, Landscape Lighting Plan, Site Plans
    Mason S. Hicks Architects; Hicks-Willis Architects; John Talbert & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field), 1969 (Tube 834)
    Site Plan, Parking Area Irrigation Plan
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field) (Tube 861)
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport (Grannis Field) (Tube 50)
    Schematic development plan
  - Fayetteville Municipal Airport: Rental car service areas, 1968 (Tube 711)
    Site Plan, Sections and Details, Planting Plans
    Mason S. Hicks Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Museum of Art, 1980 (Tube 865)
    Aerial Photograph
    Johnson Dick Photographer; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville Museum of Art: Clark Gardens, 1980 (Tube 164)
  - Fayetteville Museum of Art, Incorporated, 1978 (Tube 283)
  - Fayetteville Museum of Art, Incorporated, 1979 (Tube 303)
  - Fayetteville Museum of Art, Incorporated, 1977 (Tube 300)
  - Fayetteville Museum of Art, Incorporated, 1978-1980 (Tube 849)
    Planting Plan, Site Plan, Landscape Design
  - Fayetteville photogrammetric maps (1 of 3), 1960 (Tube 637)
  - Fayetteville photogrammetric maps (2 of 3), 1960 (Tube 638)
  - Fayetteville photogrammetric maps (3 of 3), 1960 (Tube 639)
  - Fayetteville Police Station, 1995 (Tube 441)
    Design Development
    MacMillan-Ellinwood Design Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Fayetteville State College (1 of 2), 1966 (Tube 456)
    Master Plan: Initial Development, 1967-1975; Existing Conditions Map; Analysis of Topography; Analysis of Proposed Campus
  - Fayetteville State College (2 of 2), 1966 (Tube 780)
    Master plans
  - Fayetteville State College, 1966-1969 (Tube 787)
    Master Plan
  - Fayetteville State University, 1968 (Tube 779)
    Land acquisition plan, signage
  - Fayetteville Street Elementary School, 1962 (Tube 813)
  - Fearrington Farm, 1974 (Flatfolder 32)
    Chatham County (N.C.)
  - Fearrington Farm (1 of 3), 1974 (Tube 507)
    Preliminary Plat
  - Fearrington Farm (2 of 3), 1974 (Tube 770)
    Preliminary plat, pottery shop
  - Fearrington Farm (3 of 3), 1974 (Tube 789)
    Topographic Plan, Village, Phasing Plan, Soils, Land Forms, Preliminary Plat, Slopes, Existing, Elevation, Vicinity, Concept, First Studies/Plan
  - Federal Place Downtown, 1975 (Tube 773)
    Proposed development plan, site location plan
    Bell Design Group; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Ferdon (Ben and Jane) residence, 2002 (Tube 231)
  - Ferebee (Mr. and Mrs. S. Scott, Jr.) residence, 1968 (Tube 843)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Fergus Garden Restaurant (Tube 456)
  - Fergus Garden Restaurant, 1965 (Tube 711)
    Enlarged Staking Plan, Planting Plan No. 1, Staking Plan
  - Fidelity Bank: Parking entrance, 1974 (Tube 787)
    Bell Design Group; Cary (N.C.)
  - Figure Eight Island South End, 1971 (Tube 720)
    Property Ownership Map
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Figure Eight Island (N.C.)
  - Figure Eight Island (1 of 3), 1972 (Tube 885)
    New Hanover County (N.C.)
  - Figure Eight Island (2 of 3), 1972 (Tube 886)
  - Figure Eight Island (3 of 3), 1972 (Tube 894)
    New Hanover County (N.C.); Figure Eight Island (N.C.)
  - Finch (Jack and Judy) property (Tube 30)
    Preliminary Land Use and Subdivision Plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; High Point (N.C.)
  - Finch (Jack and Judy) property (Tube 31)
  - Finch (John Lambeth) property: Sturbridge Woods, 1991 (Tube 37)
  - Finch (Mr. and Mrs. T.A.) residence: Phase 2 of Finch/Ragan subdivision, 1976 (Tube 30)
    Bell Design Group; Thomasville (N.C.)
  - Finkel (Alan and Marty) residence (1 of 2), 1992 (Tube 645)
    Shawcroft Associates, Architects; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Oxford (N.C.)
  - Finkel (Alan and Marty) residence, 1990 (Tube 846)
    Details and Sections
    McKimmon, Edwards, & Shawcroft; Oxford (N.C.)
  - Finkel (Alan and Marty) residence (2 of 2), 1992 (Tube 847)
    Landscape Master Plan, Site Plans
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; McKimmon, Edwards, & Shawcroft; Shawcroft Associates, Architects; Oxford (N.C.)
  - First Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1968 (Tube 814)
    Planting plan, plant list
    Harrell & Clark Architects; Blowing Rock (N.C.)
  - First Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1968 (Tube 712)
    Details, Plant List and Planting Notes, Landscape Development Plan
  - First Citizen Bank & Trust Co., 1973 (Tube 715)
    Alleyway: Grading and Lighting Plan, Staking Plan, Preliminary Plan, Planting Plan; Site Plan, Preliminary Plan, Elevations, Details
    Bell Design Group; Selma (N.C.)
  - First Citizen Bank & Trust Co., 1974 (Tube 715)
    Sign Plan, Details, Revised Planting Plan
    McGee Harry Kirk 1909?-; Bell Design Group; Warrenton (N.C.)
  - First Citizens Bank and Trust Co.: Drive in bank, 1962 (Tube 50)
    Landscape plan and details
  - First Federal Plaza, 1967 (Tube 503)
    Specifications
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Danville (Va.)
  - First Federal Plaza: First Federal Savings and Loan Association (1 of 4), 1967 (Tube 794)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Danville (Va.)
  - First Federal Plaza: First Federal Savings and Loan Association (2 of 4), 1967 (Tube 847)
    Utility Plan
  - First Federal Plaza: First Federal Savings and Loan Association (3 of 4), 1967 (Tube 700)
    Specifications, Landscape Plans
    Robert W. Thompson & Donald R. Evans, Associated Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Danville (Va.)
  - First Federal Plaza: First Federal Savings and Loan Association (4 of 4), 1967 (Tube 793)
    Landscape Plan, Details, Planting Plan, Staking Plan & Section, Construction of Grading and Staking Plan, Grading Plan and Section, Pool Sections and Details
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, 1979-1980 (Tube 684)
    Planting and landscape development
    Bell Design Group; Skinner-Lamm, PA; Goldsboro (N.C.)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, 1979 (Tube 685)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan (Tube 739)
    Leif Valand & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, 1968 (Tube 787)
    Haskins & Rice, Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Zebulon (N.C.)
  - First Methodist Church, 1967 (Tube 814)
    Planting plan, staking plan, grading plan
  - First Methodist Church, 1966 (Tube 826)
  - First National Bank of Eastern N.C. (Tube 843)
    Overall Site Plans
    Dunn (N.C.)
  - First Presbyterian Church, 1968 (Tube 843)
    Interior Court Garden
  - Fisher (Mr. and Mrs. D.T.) residence, 1970 (Tube 712)
  - Fisher's Restaurant, 1961 (Tube 813)
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Wilmington (N.C.)
  - Fishman (Mr. and Mrs. Maurice) residence, 1966 (Tube 843)
    Plant List, Landscape Plans
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - FitzGerald (Rev. and Mrs. F. Owen) residence (1 of 2), 1976 (Tube 144)
    Site plan showing planting
  - FitzGerald (Rev. and Mrs. F. Owen) residence (2 of 2), 1976 (Tube 145)
  - Five Oaks Lake Side Townhomes (Tube 258)
  - Five Oaks Lake Side Townhomes, 1985 (Tube 261)
    Site plan, phase map
    Design Collective, Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Five Oaks Lakeside, 1985-1987 (Tube 853)
    Sign Elevation and Sections, Planting Plan and Details, Sign: Site Plan, Construction Details
    Bell Design Group; Cimarron Capital, Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Five Oaks Lakeside, 1986 (Tube 859)
    Section Two Phase Map, Site Plan
  - Five residences on New Garden Road at Academy Street intersection, 1990 (Tube 134)
    Concept of landscape improvement plan
  - Fleming Street School, 1967 (Tube 843)
    Dudley & Shoe Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Greenville (N.C.)
  - Flora McKinnon McNeil Memorial Garden: St. Andrews Presbyterian College, 1963 (Tube 796)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Laurinburg (N.C.)
  - Floyd (Holly, Turner, and Drexel) residence, 1999 (Flatfolder 19)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Southern Pines (N.C.)
  - Floyd (Holly, Turner, and Drexel) residence (1 of 4), 1999-2000 (Tube 421)
    Planting plan, swimming pool details, lighting details
  - Floyd (Holly, Turner, and Drexel) residence (2 of 4), 1999-2000 (Tube 422)
    Swimming pool elevations and details, staking and grading plan, topographic survey
  - Floyd (Holly, Turner, and Drexel) residence (3 of 4), 1999-2000 (Tube 423)
    Staking and grading, swimming pool elevations and details, landscape development plan
  - Floyd (Holly, Turner, and Drexel) residence (4 of 4), 1999-2000 (Tube 424)
    Topographic map, planting plan, landscape development plan, planting notes, staking and grading plan
  - Floyd (John and Holly) residence, 1991 (Tube 645)
    Master landscape plan
  - Floyd (Mr. and Mrs. A.S.) residence, 1964 (Tube 826)
  - Flythe (Mr. and Mrs. James T.) residence, 1993 (Tube 847)
    Construction Details, Planting Plan
  - Flythe (Mr. and Mrs. James T.) residence, 1992 (Tube 846)
    Sections, Exteriors Elevations/Sections, Exterior Elevations, Second Floor Plan
    Mogilinicki Edwin E.; Wake County (N.C.)
  - Forest Hills Shopping Center, 1973 (Tube 629)
    Large Hand-drawn Area Map
    Bell Design Group; Smith, Mills & Associates; Garner (N.C.)
  - Forest Hills Shopping Center, 1973 (Tube 630)
    Topographic Map, Soil Plan, Land Unites Plan
    Landmark Engineering Co., Inc.; Bell Design Group; Smith, Mills & Associates; Garner (N.C.)
  - Fort Bragg Main Post N.C.O. Motel, 1966 (Tube 739)
    Planting Plan, Staking, Grading, and Irrigation Plans
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Fort Bragg (N.C.)
  - Fort Bragg N.C.O. Open Mess and Facilities, 1966 (Tube 700)
  - Foster (Mr. and Mrs. Vernon G.) residence (1 of 2), 1974 (Tube 700)
    Preliminary Landscape Plan, Details, Planting Plan, Detail Indications, Staking Plan
  - Foster (Mr. and Mrs. Vernon G.) residence (2 of 2), 1974 (Tube 787)
  - Foster (Vernon G.), 1974 (Tube 780)
    Forsyth County (N.C.)
  - Foushee Housing Project, 1970 (Tube 688)
    Bell Design Group; Richard C. Bell Associates; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Foxwood Drive area (Tube 863)
    Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Freelove (Bill and Sally) residence (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Second Floor Plan
  - Freelove (Bill and Sally) residence, 1989 (Flatfolder 23)
  - Freelove (Bill and Sally) residence, 1981-1983 (Tube 170)
    Detailed staking plan, detailed grading plan, detailed plan, detailed development plan
  - Freelove (Bill and Sally) residence, 1981 (Tube 212)
    Detailed plans
  - Freelove (Bill and Sally) residence, 1981-1982 (Tube 556)